Hey everyone and welcome to a new jumpsuit up video here on my channel. I'm
Celine and it's been a while since the last jumpsuit up video because I've been
busy doing other videos as you can see on my channel but today we're back at it
and I have this really cool silver catsuit from GoGuy clothing. That's why
I'm wearing this kind of start outfit to set the mood a bit and I think I'm going
to change into this one right away.
This is a lot of fun outfit, especially the color and I combined it with funny shoes because
I thought well black is not going to fit and I also love the gloves which are not attached
but they look like they are from afar at least.
Okay, GoGuy clothing is a UK based brand for club wear and party outfits but also street wear.
So you can have a look at their shop. There's really a lot to see.
And the specialty is that they only do collections.
So you don't have the regular basic all-time articles.
But if it's sold out, it's gone.
So while I'm recording this, the catsuit is probably still available.
although not in this color I'm going to tell you about it in a sec but normally it should be in
the shop now and I hope when you see the video it still is there. I saw this catsuit in the color
black which is how it is offered regularly but then I wrote to Gorgai and asked hey can you do
the catsuit in a different color because I saw this material in this color in a short legged
catsuit and they were like yeah sure we can do that for you and so here I am wearing this silver
catsuit with long arms and long legs thanks for that go guy
specialties here are the seams along the catsuit also to the back because it's kind of like
padded piping seam so it's three-dimensional and it gives a bit of structure to the catsuit
and also supports the catsuit that it stays where it should stay and also I think it enhances
the look of the body a lot because you have these lines where the eye can yeah hang along on hang on
Anyway, it's a cool look and I think this is really unique, this cut.
So I'm really happy to show it to you here.
For the photoshoot I did with the catsuit I styled my hair in two braids to have this
like festival vibe.
And also I've worn these glasses so you can go to, I don't know, a rave or an Ibiza party
with them.
It's a pretty fun look.
But I'm going to show you a second shoe option now.
Okay, I went with a contrast color now for the high heels because I know that a lot of
you don't like these plateau boots but to be honest, if I'm going out, I'm definitely
wearing the plateau boots and not the high heels because it's just much more comfy and
easier.
You can see here that the legs are really long which is a big big plus point.
Also the arms and the material is kind of a PU matte PVC if you want to compare it to
something.
So not latex.
So if you like this look check out the GoGuy webshop they ship worldwide which is really
cool.
So I'm not from UK either but I still got it.
And thank you GoGuy for the collaboration.
Thank you for watching this video.
Have a look at my other videos.
I have a lot more jumpsuit videos but also a lot of different stuff.
And see you in the next video.
Bye.